[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the third Aladdin movie made by Disney?", "correct_answer": "Aladdin and the King of Thieves", "incorrect_answers": ["The Return of Jafar", "None of these", "Aladdin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Deputy Marshall Harvey Pell in High Noon?", "correct_answer": "Lloyd Bridges", "incorrect_answers": ["Lon Chaney, Jr.", "Otto Kruger", "Harry Morgan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are theories that Neanderthals actually buried their dead.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "September 3rd through 13th in the year 1752 did not exist.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that the maximum score you can get on SAT is 2400?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following films was not directed by Bernardo Bertolucci?", "correct_answer": "The Prestige", "incorrect_answers": ["The Last Emperor", "Last Tango in Paris", "The Conformist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1993 film was honored with the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 66th Academy Awards ceremony in 1994?", "correct_answer": "Schindlers List", "incorrect_answers": ["The Remains of the Day", "The Fugitive", "In the Name of the Father"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did the Black Plague  originate?", "correct_answer": "India", "incorrect_answers": ["Turkey", "Italy", "Russia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was/were the first passenger/s on a hot air balloon?", "correct_answer": "all of these", "incorrect_answers": ["s rooster", "a duck", "sheep"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did the Castelo Branco cheese originate?", "correct_answer": "Portugal", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Italy", "Brazil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Jake Ryans girlfriend in the movie Sixteen Candles?", "correct_answer": "Caroline Mulford", "incorrect_answers": ["Samantha Baker", "Caroline Inthecity", "Eve Quizeditor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call the longest day of the year?", "correct_answer": "The summer solstice", "incorrect_answers": ["The winter equinox", "The summer equinox", "The winter solstice"]}]